Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 2003 (Box 74-76)
  - N.J. Sch. Bd. Ass'n Ins. Group v. Dean Witter Reynolds, Inc. 2003 October 07 (Box 75)
  - Oldhamv. Weeks Marine, Inc. 2003 February 14 (Box 75)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit I; Exhibit II
  - Pascal v. Ashcroft 2003 July 07 (Box 75)
  - Pazden v. Maurer 2003 September 25 (Box 75)
    Opinion; Order; Order (2003 October 03)
  - Perez v. Fed. Bureau of Investigation 2003 April 03 (Box 75)
  - Petchem v. Capacity Coverage Co. 2003 October 31 (Box 75)
  - Pinker v. Roche Holdings 2003 February 05 (Box 75)
    Consumer Product Safety Commission
  - Pomales v. Moore 2003 March 28 (Box 75)
  - Quaid v. Immigration & Naturalization Serv. 2003 April 24 (Box 76)
    Yemen
  - Raftree v. First Investors Corp. 2003 March 14 (Box 76)
  - Rhett v. Union County Div. of Soc. Serv. 2003 December 29 (Box 76)
  - Ries v. Comm'r 2003 June 30 (Box 76)
  - Ryan v. Mineta 2003 December 16 (Box 76)
  - Schering Corp. v. Perrigo Co. 2003 October 31 (Box 76)
    Food and Drug Administration (FDA)
  - Sims v. Fed. Express Corp. 2003 January 17 (Box 76)
  - Smithkline Beecham Corp. v. Teva Pharm. 2003 March 05 (Box 76)
    Opinion; Order; Order (2003 March 11)
  - Soto v. Ace Mills, Inc. 2003 November 25 (Box 76)
  - Tardy v. Comm'r 2003 June 04 (Box 76)
  - Tasty Fries v. Romanoff 2003 June 13 (Box 76)
  - Total Car Franchising Corp. v. Wilhovsky 2003 July 24 (Box 76)
  - United States v. Dougle 2003 January 13 (Box 76)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2003 October 20)
  - Vulcan Pioneers of N.J. v. City of Newark 2003 May 27 (Box 76)
    Emergency planning and evacuation
  - Wells Fargo Funding v. Premier Mortgage Corp. 2003 June 17 (Box 76)
  - Wilkins v. Dep't of Veterans Affairs 2003 June 24 (Box 76)
  - Worsley v. U.S. Marshals Serv. 2003 September 10 (Box 76)
    Letter-Opinion; Exhibit A
  - Yost v. Rutgers Univ. 2003 September 29 (Box 76)
- Papers, 2004 (Box 77-78)
  All papers dated 2004.
  - Abdur-Rahman v. Anheuser-Busch 2004 September 27 (Box 77)
    National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
  - All American Ford v. Market Scan Information Sys. 2004 January 22 (Box 77)
  - Asahi Kogaku Kogyo KK v. Samsung Opto-Elec. Am. 2004 December 07 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (2004 August 05)
  - Bishop v. State 2004 January 19 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 August 16)
  - Brahmbhatt v. Ridge 2004 July 07 (Box 77)
    Department of Homeland Security
    India
  - Branch v. Ventura 2004 October 12 (Box 77)
  - Burlington Outlet Mall Joint Venture Prop. v. M.C. Mgmt. 2004 July 12 (Box 77)
    Women in business
  - Coe v. Potter 2004 July 07 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 July 15)
  - Corwin v. Ernst & Young 2004 August 11 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order [undated]
  - Danvers Motor Co. v. Ford Motor Co. 2004 January 27 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 September 30)
  - In re DeNofa 2004 January 27 (Box 77)
  - Directv v. Cimiluca 2004 January 26 (Box 77)
    Directv v. Cimiluca, No. 03-2422, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 27997 (D. N.J. Jan. 26, 2004).
  - Doherty v. Teamsters Pension Trust Fund 2004 July 12 (Box 77)
  - Dzielo v. Barnhart 2004 March 25 (Box 77)
  - Emeline Publ'n v. Perfect 10, Inc. 2004 January 30 (Box 77)
  - Evans v. Port Auth. Trans-Hudson Corp. 2004 September 24 (Box 77)
    Commuting
  - Falcone v. Hendricks 2004 January 19 (Box 77)
  - Fisher v. Sherrer 2004 February 09 (Box 77)
  - Greenwich Ins. Co. v. 143 W. Assoc. 2004 December 01 (Box 77)
  - Greg Manning Auctions v. Fulmer 2004 June 16 (Box 77)
  - Hartford Fire Ins. Co. v. Stallion Indus. 2004 February 13 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 February 17)
  - Hayes v. Abode 2004 March 12 (Box 77)
  - Heslop v. Immigration & Naturalization Serv. 2004 March 01 (Box 77)
  - Immigration & Naturalization Serv. Detainees v. Middlesex County 2004 September 30 (Box 77)
  - Jackmon v. N.J. Dep't of Corr. 2004 September 30 (Box 77)
  - Jackson v. Brown 2004 January 30 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 March 11)
  - Johnson v. Hendricks 2004 May 05 (Box 77)
  - Kelley v. Comm'r 2004 June 30 (Box 77)
    Kelley v. Comm'r, No. 02-3572, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 28407 (D. N.J. June 30, 2004).
  - La Salle Nat'l Bank v. First Conn. Holding Group 2004 June 29 (Box 77)
  - Meyer v. Kent 2004 March 26 (Box 77)
    Meyer v. Kent, No. 01-5836, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 28834 (D. N.J. Mar. 26, 2004).
  - Mierzwa v. City of Garfield 2004 July 28 (Box 77)
    Opinion; Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 December 20); Opinion; Order (2004 December 23)
  - Moya v. State Farm Ins. Co. 2004 June 28 (Box 77)
  - Muniz v. Hendricks 2004 March 29 (Box 78)
  - Perez v. Comm'r 2004 September 30 (Box 78)
  - Peterson v. Newark Police Dep't 2004 June 21 (Box 78)
  - Rage Games Ltd. v. Majesco Sales, Inc. 2004 July 15 (Box 78)
  - Rajaram v. Barnhart 2004 January 30 (Box 78)
  - Redding v. Corning 2004 July 07 (Box 78)
    Redding v. Corning, No. 04-1971, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 29145 (D. N.J. July 7, 2004).
  - Reveron v. Tycom, Inc. 2004 September 30 (Box 78)
    Reveron v. Tycom, Inc., No. 02-3599, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 26667 (D. N.J. Sept. 30, 2004).
  - Rhett v. Union County Div. of Soc. Serv. 2004 February 18 (Box 78)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Univ. Hosp. v. Thompson 2004 April 15 (Box 78)
    Robert Wood Johnson Univ. Hosp. v. Thompson, No. 04-142, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 6893 (D. N.J. Jan. 14, 2004).; No. 04-142, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 8498 (D. N.J. Apr. 15, 2004).
  - Rodriguez v. Comm'r 2004 March 26 (Box 78)
  - Roulhac v. Newark Beth Israel Med. Ctr. 2004 July 15 (Box 78)
  - In re Royal Dutch/Shell Transp. Sec. Litig. 2004 June 30 (Box 78)
    Opinion; Order; Order; Opinion; Order (2004 August 03)
    Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)
  - Ryan v. Slater 2004 January 30 (Box 78)
  - Sanders v. Trinitas Hosp. 2004 October 25 (Box 78)
    Sanders v. Trinitas Hosp., No. 02-1655, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 28506 (D. N.J. Oct. 25, 2004).
  - Scott v. Barnhart 2004 July 12 (Box 78)
  - Smithkline Beecham Corp. v. Teva Pharm. 2004 July 15 (Box 78)
    Smithkline Beecham Corp. v. Teva Pharm., No. 02-3779, 2004 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 26603 (D. N.J. July 15, 2004).
  - Synergy, Inc. v. Exact Software Co. 2004 August 02 (Box 78)
  - Terminello v. City of Passaic 2004 January 22 (Box 78)
  - Thomas v. Corr. Med. Serv. 2004 December 15 (Box 78)
    Blood and blood diseases
  - Truong v. Am. Ass'n of Univ. Professors 2004 December 09 (Box 78)
    Vietnam
  - Unionamerica Ins. Co. v. D&J Towing and Recovery 2004 January 13 (Box 78)
  - United States v. $8,221,877.16 in U.S. Currency 2004 March 26 (Box 78)
    Opinion; Exhibit A; Order │ Opinion; Order (2004 July 06)
    Brazil
    Currency
  - United States v. Cimera 2004 October 07 (Box 78)
  - United States v. Marshman 2004 December 16 (Box 78)
  - Veira v. Ashcroft 2004 January 07 (Box 78)
  - Velez v. Lucent Techn. 2004 December 16 (Box 78)
  - Vulcan Pioneers of N.J. v. City of Newark 2004 August 20 (Box 78)
  - Woods v. County of Hudson 2004 November 23 (Box 78)
  - Yost v. Rutgers Univ. 2004 June 30 (Box 78)
- Papers, 2005 (Box 79-80)
  All papers dated 2005.
  - Abreu v. United States 2005 August 15 (Box 79)
    Abreu v. United States, No. 03-2961, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18085 (D. N.J. Aug. 15, 2005).
  - Adegbuji v. Fifteen Immigration & Customs Enforcement Agents 2005 January 06 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 August 15)
  - Alcantara v. United States 2005 August 30 (Box 79)
    Alcantara v. United States, No. 03-3385, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 36526 (D. N.J. Aug. 30, 2005).
  - Allure Home Creation v. Zak Designs 2005 August 10 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Exhibit PM 2 (2); Exhibit PM 3; Order; Order (2005 August 15)
    Allure Home Creation v. Zak Designs, No. 03-193, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 17059 (D. N.J. Aug. 10, 2005).
  - Almahdi v. Rodriguez 2005 April 26 (Box 79)
  - Anderson v. Operating Eng'r, Local 68 2005 May 25 (Box 79)
  - Beasley v. Fletcher 2005 January 06 (Box 79)
  - Bernardi v. United States 2005 June 09 (Box 79)
  - Brown v. Catholic Cmty. Serv. 2005 August 15 (Box 79)
    Brown v. Catholic Cmty. Serv., No. 05-837, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18159 (D. N.J. Aug. 15, 2005).
  - Buck v. Reick 2005 July 13 (Box 79)
  - Bus. Edge Group v. Champion Mortgage Co. 2005 August 29 (Box 79)
    Bus. Edge Group v. Champion Mortgage Co., No. 03-5498, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 36585 (D. N.J. Aug. 29, 2005).
  - Camillo v. Hendricks 2005 August 17 (Box 79)
    Camillo v. Hendricks, No. 03-1297, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18146 (D. N.J. Aug. 17, 2005).
  - Campbell v. Chase Manhattan Bank 2005 June 24 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 August 09)
    Campbell v. Chase Manhattan Bank, No. 02-3489, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16402 (D. N.J. June 24, 2005).; No. 02-3489, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 43026 (D. N.J. Aug. 9, 2005).
  - Central Lewmar v. Gentilin 2005 June 01 (Box 79)
    Central Lewmar v. Gentilin, No. 03-4671, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 45902 (D. N.J. June 1, 2005).
  - Chao v. N.J. Licensed Beverage Ass'n 2005 May 17 (Box 79)
  - Cradle v. Brooks 2005 July 11 (Box 79)
    Cradle v. Brooks, No. 02-2121, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 33417 (D. N.J. July 11, 2005).
  - Directv v. Cimiluca 2005 January 07 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Exhibit A; Exhibit B; Order (2005 March 08)
    Directv v. Cimiluca, No. 03-2422, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 10677 (D. N.J. Mar. 8, 2005).
  - Doumit v. Publishers Circulation Fulfillment 2005 March 30 (Box 79)
  - Dunkin' Donuts v. Arkay Donuts 2005 April 13 (Box 79)
    Dunkin' Donuts v. Arkay Donuts, No. 05-387, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 43540 (D. N.J. Apr. 13, 2005).
  - Fed. Trade Comm'n v. Check Investors, Inc. 2005 July 15 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Final Order for Judgment and Permanent Injunction as to Defendants
    Fed. Trade Comm'n v. Check Investors, Inc., No. 03-2115, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 34349 (D. N.J. July 15, 2005).; No. 03-2115, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 37199 (D. N.J. July 18, 2005).
  - Giraldo v. United States 2005 August 11 (Box 79)
    Giraldo v. United States, No. 04-709, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16862 (D. N.J. Aug. 11, 2005).
  - Gonzalez v. Passaic County Prob. 2005 August 24 (Box 79)
    Gonzalez v. Passaic County Prob., No. 04-3001, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18890 (D. N.J. Aug. 24, 2005).
  - Gonzalez v. United States 2005 August 30 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Transcript of Proceedings (Sentence); Exhibit B; Exhibit C; Order
    Gonzalez v. United States, No. 99-1183, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 38496 (D. N.J. Aug. 30, 2005).
  - Gotowicz v. Ashcroft 2005 February 16 (Box 79)
  - Greg Manning Auctions v. Fulmer 2005 August 23 (Box 79)
  - Hernandez v. Immigration & Naturalization Serv. 2005 February 17 (Box 79)
  - Hug v. Nia Group 2005 March 07 (Box 79)
  - Jackus v. Elizabeth Bd. of Ed. 2005 March 04 (Box 79)
  - Janssen Pharm. v. Mylan Pharm. 2005 February 07 (Box 79)
  - Johnson v. Polo Ralph Lauren Corp. 2005 August 03 (Box 79)
  - Landeta v. Comm'r 2005 May 16 (Box 79)
  - Lomack v. City of Newark 2005 August 24 (Box 79)
    Opinion; Plaintiff's Exhibit 4; Plaintiff's Exhibit 5; Plaintiff's Exhibit 6; Order
    Lomack v. City of Newark, No. 04-6085, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18892 (D. N.J. Aug. 24, 2005).
  - Lukovitch v. Wal-Mart Stores 2005 December 17 (Box 80)
  - Luzardo v. United States 2005 August 15 (Box 80)
    Luzardo v. United States, No. 03-2962, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18148 (D. N.J. Aug. 15, 2005).
  - Mierzwa v. City of Garfield 2005 April 18 (Box 80)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 August 24)
    Mierzwa v. City of Garfield, No. 04-5268, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18880 (D. N.J. Aug. 24, 2005).
  - Milton v. Comm'r 2005 June 28 (Box 80)
  - Nash Distrib. v. Guinness Bass Imp. Co. 2005 June 03 (Box 80)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 August 25)
  - Nieves v. Comm'r 2005 August 30 (Box 80)
  - O'Callaghan v. Harvey 2005 March 10 (Box 80)
  - Papazacharis v. Cont'l Airlines 2005 July 28 (Box 80)
  - Peterson v. Newark Police Dep't 2005 August 24 (Box 80)
  - Pentax Corp. v. Samsung Opto-Elec. Am. 2005 March 30 (Box 80)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 April 18)
  - Perez v. United States 2005 August 30 (Box 80)
    Perez v. United States, No. 03-4610, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 36382 (D. N.J. Aug. 30, 2005).
  - Prince v. Howmet Corp. 2005 April 28 (Box 80)
    Prince v. Howmet Corp., No. 03-5434, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16035 (D. N.J. Apr. 28, 2005).
  - Redding v. Owens Corning Co. 2005 August 03 (Box 80)
    Redding v. Owens Corning Co., No. 04-1971, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16406 (D. N.J. Aug. 3, 2005).
  - Rivera v. Arvonio 2005 March 01 (Box 80)
  - Robinson v. Comm'r 2005 August 30 (Box 80)
  - In re Royal Dutch/Shell Transp. Sec. Litig. 2005 February 15 (Box 80)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 August 09) │ Order (2005 August 15) │ Order (2005 August 23)
    U.S. and foreign investments
    International finance and foreign exchange
    Texas
    In re Royal Dutch/Shell Transp. Sec. Litig., 380 F. Supp. 2d 509 (D. N.J. 2005).
  - Sanders v. Trinitas Hosp. 2005 August 24 (Box 80)
    Sanders v. Trinitas Hosp., No. 02-1655, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18985 (D. N.J. Aug. 24, 2005).
  - Silver v. Am. Inst. of Certified Pub. Accountants 2005 August 15 (Box 80)
    Silver v. Am. Inst. of Certified Pub. Accountants, No. 01-4910, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18108 (D. N.J. Aug. 15, 2005).
  - Sisters of St. Dominic v. Allied Irish Bank 2005 March 10 (Box 80)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2005 August 10)
    Sisters of St. Dominic v. Allied Irish Bank, No. 03-3078, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 17032 (D. N.J. Aug. 10, 2005).
  - Smith v. United States 2005 August 24 (Box 80)
  - Smithkline Beecham Corp. v. Teva Pharm. 2005 January 13 (Box 80)
  - Solis v. Ashcroft 2005 February 28 (Box 80)
    Opinion; Release Order
  - Solis v. United States 2005 August 15 (Box 80)
  - Tait v. City of Totowa Police Dep't 2005 March 10 (Box 80)
  - Terminello v. City of Passaic 2005 April 21 (Box 80)
  - United States v. $8,221,877.16 in U.S. Currency 2005 February 10 (Box 80)
  - United States v. Pires de Almeida 2005 March 07 (Box 80)
  - Wash v. United States 2005 August 15 (Box 80)
    Wash v. United States, No. 05-108, 2005 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18152 (D. N.J. Aug. 15, 2005).
  - Yarosh v. Salkind 2005 June 20 (Box 80)
  - Yost v. Rutgers Univ. 2005 March 08 (Box 80)